financialservicesonline.com.au 2017-02-18

# Our Privacy Policy Statement | Public Liability | FinancialServicesOnline.com.au

### Financial Services Online Privacy Statement

Our privacy policy statement has been created to demonstrate our respect for your privacy. Below we have outlined how we manage the personal�information that we gather.

### The information we gather and and how we use it.

In order for us to attend to your request for financial services advice, information or comparative quotes, we need to know your name and contact details along with any other data that is directly relevant to the specific enquiry that you are making.

Our third part network product and service providers then use this information to tailor financial solutions to your specific needs and to advise you accordingly. This information is referred to those providers on your behalf so they can provide a product or service to you. (Unless we advise you to the contrary, these businesses have no right to utilise any personally identifiable data that you provide other than what is required in order to provide the assistance you seek from us.)

Your contact details and other personal information that you provide to us will not be shared with any other person or entity at any time.

### Cookies

We utilise cookies to collect session information and user-specific data on which pages on our website that you access or visit in order to track your progress through our web site in order for us to to improve the performance of our website.

### Advertising

We use third-party advertising companies to serve our ads on our website. These third-party advertising companies employ cookies and 1x1 pixel .gifs or web beacons to measure and improve the effectiveness of ads for their clients. To do so, these companies may use anonymous information about your visits to our website and other websites. This information can include: date/time of banner ad shown, the banner ad that was shown, their cookie, the IP address. This information can also be used for online preference marketing purposes.

### Access your Personal Information

If you wish, you can access information supplied to us other than in a few circumstance that are set out under Australian law. Financial Services Online reserves the right to determine how the data is accessed. In the event that access to your data is denied, you will be provided with a written explanation as to why and, subject to the reason behind the denial, we may provide access to your data through mutually agreeable intermediaries to meet your needs oand ours. 

Information access may be subject to a nominal charge to enable us to recoup any reasonable direct or indirect expenses incurred by us in order to satisfy your request.

Please feel free to [contact us](http://www.financialservicesonline.com.au/contact_us.htm) should you require access to your personal information. To ensure the protection of your personal data, we may ask that your request be written.

### Privacy Policy Changes

We will review our privacy statement from time to time to ensure that it meets the expectations of the market and any regulatory requirements.

### Feedback

Please [contact us](http://www.financialservicesonline.com.au/contact_us.htm) should you experience any difficulties or problems in respect� to our privacy policy or the management of your personal information. 

Further information about privacy issues and the protection of your personal information is obtainable from the Australian Federal Privacy Commissioner on: 1300 363 992.

### Complaints

You are invited to lodge a complaint with us if you consider that we have breached this Privacy Policy or the National Privacy Principles.

We will respond promptly to complaints. 

In order to lodge a complaint, please [contact us](http://www.financialservicesonline.com.au/contact_us.htm) in the first instance. If you are not satisfied with our response to your complaint, you can telephone the Australian Federal Privacy Commissioner's hotline on: 1300 363 992.

If you have any question about this privacy statement, the practices of our website, or your dealings with our website, you can [contact us](http://www.financialservicesonline.com.au/contact_us.htm)
